Hi.
And this was some I want to talk with you about wind surf context.
So context is anything is related to your question or your problem to the wind surf, everything
makes sense to look any examples, additional information, which can help to improve the accuracy
of the result.
So let's talk about the default context, what wind surf automatically used as a context.
So, it used as a context, a current file and other open files in your code editor, like
it used the file names as a file structure to understand what is your problem about what
is your project, what is your context.
It also used your entire local code based, indexed to find some relevant code snippets
as you work, because sometimes you know, specify the clear files you need to look and
wind surf is looking for your code based to find the relevant information.
Also, for pro users, there is more context length, so you can keep more files, more data
as a context, you have bigger index limits and more custom opinion context, like you have
more possibilities, it's for pro plan.
Teams and enterprise also have all these features, they additionally are able to index
remote repositories, like other projects and it might be helpful when you work in a cross
multiple repost.
So let's now talk about some best practice for opinion and context, what you need to
pin, so you should pin only what you need, because if you pin too much, it can slow
things down.
So what is useful to pin some class or struct definitions files from other models, which
should relate to your question.
The framework library code examples, for example, if you created a new component, you
can mention the old components just to be an example in what file you write code and what
file you expect the component should be.
You can place the files for specific interface, I know some configuration, which might
help AI to understand better what you want to get from him.
Also you can put as a context, some small folder with small files you work in, like if you
work in a feature and you have feature folder, you can put all the feature folder to get
an information about some related files, or you can put just the file what you're going
to test, you can mention some details files, some small files, and just ask for AI to write
the test, so we don't know what files you mean.
There is a functions functionality in WinServe, I will show you later how to use it and where
you find it.
So when you chat in WinServe, you can use the mention to bring specific part of code
by in the conversation, and as you mentioned, it will always be included in the response,
so AI will analyze it, where you can mention, you can mention function classes in supported
languages, so it supports really a lot of languages, you can mention files and directories
in your code base, you can mention some remote repositories and you can mention some terminal
contacts, some commands, etcetera, when you mean the remote repositories, you can mention
just the link on repository, which should be an example, so now let's dive into WinServe
and I will show you how to use it, so right here you see you can ask anything and mention,
you should use this special symbol to mention, you can use it, and choose whatever you want,
another option how to do it, you can click add a context and use for example you want to upload
an image, you can trigger some workflow and you can use the mention, what you have, you
have web, you can mention okay, you can search by web, you can mention some code content
items, for example mention what exactly you want, you can mention some files, or you will
see all your project files right here, you can mention the directories and mention the folder
like I have not models folder, but I'm not sure if it's visible, yep, I see it's visible
only the test folder, okay, what else you can mention, you can mention the documentation
like I know we gonna use, let's say just documentation, it's not found right here, so some
of the documentation you can just mention manually, imagine we gonna use a node, a node just
so we just mention it and can ask question about this documentation, what else, you can
use the MCP service and knowledge rules, we will talk about it in a future lessons, we
should plan into add later, you can mention the conversations, have a conversations, if you
like have something useful in them, what else, you can mention the browser, the terminal,
so we can written documentation about the browser and terminal means, but the most popular
it, as the files folder and the commentations, it's the most popular things I use in my daily
routines, so I hope it was useful for you, now you know that you can mention the context,
it's really often how we sort of provide much better answers and responses, so it's
impact the code quality and see you in the next lessons.